<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/fly-sheets-boots.atom"/>
  <title>Tack Wholesale</title>
  <updated>2018-06-25T09:55:53-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tack Wholesale</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
    <published>2018-06-25T09:55:53-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-25T09:55:53-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/derby-originals-mesh-belly-band-reflective-fly-sheet"/>
    <title>Derby Originals Mesh Belly Band Reflective Trim Horse Fly Sheet</title>
    <s:type>Fly Sheets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Derby Originals</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/80-8016_Background.jpg?v=1571609222"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Derby Originals<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Fly Sheets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            52.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Derby Originals’ premium mesh bellyband fly sheet was designed with your horse’s comfort and safety in mind. This fly sheet features a breathable mesh that helps keep your horse cool, as well as block harmful UV rays, and prevent biting insects from harming or irritating your horse. This fly sheet features new twists on the classic fly sheet design by adding back reflective strips to increase pasture visibility and safety and adding a full mesh belly band to keep insects away from your horse’s sensitive belly. The soft fleece wither relief also prevents your horse’s mane from being damaged. This blanket is fully adjustable and features adjustable chest closures, adjustable shoulder gussets, adjustable belly band straps, and adjustable crossed leg straps.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Features</strong></p>
<ul></ul>
<p>KEEPS PESTS AWAY - this fly sheet was designed to help protect your horse’s body, chest, and belly from biting insects and pests. Insects are unable to get through the mesh to bite at your horse, in turn preventing sores, irritation, and wounds from bug bites or reactions to them.</p>
<p>COMFORTABLE FIT - our fly sheets have a soft fleece wither relief to prevent mane damage, soft trim covering the edges of the blanket, and are made with a mesh that won’t rub your horse’s fur or irritate their skin. The crossed leg straps are designed to prevent slippage or chafing.</p>
<p>REFLECTIVE TRIM - the back corners of this fly sheet have strips of reflective material sewn onto them so that your horse will be visible from even great distances at night, making your horse more visible and safe at pasture, especially during times like hunting season!</p>
<p>BREATHABLE DESIGN - this fly sheet is designed with a lightweight but strong mesh body that is breathable and helps keep your horse cool, while also keeping bugs away from them.</p>
<p>ADJUSTABLE FIT - this fly sheet features adjustable shoulder gussets that allow your horse to move more freely, along with two adjustable chest straps and an adjustable belly band and leg straps in order to make sure your horse gets the best fit possible.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Directions</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This product should be placed on your horse and used to keep biting insects and other pests away, protect your horse from harmful UV<span> </span>rays<span> </span>and help keep your horse cool. This fly sheet can be used in the barn or pasture.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>69&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>72&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>75&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>78&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>81&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>84&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Derby Originals</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Full Horse Blankets &amp; Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SummerSale2018</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
      <title>69&quot; / Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">52.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8016BL-69</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
      <title>72&quot; / Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">52.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8016BL-72</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
      <title>75&quot; / Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">52.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8016BL-75</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
      <title>78&quot; / Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">52.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8016BL-78</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
      <title>81&quot; / Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">52.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8016BL-81</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1361</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/729494061116</id>
      <title>84&quot; / Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">52.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8016BL-84</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1361</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
    <published>2017-06-09T11:19:06-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-06-09T11:19:06-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/80-8005"/>
    <title>Derby Originals Classic Woven Cotton Hunter Beige Plaid Horse Summer Sheet</title>
    <s:type>Stable Sheets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Derby Originals</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/derby-orginals-plaid-sheet-_Main_80-8005.jpg?v=1597159279"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Derby Originals<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Stable Sheets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ou</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">r </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classic Lightweight Hunter Beige Plaid Horse Summer Sheet</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a must have for every horse owner: whether you need a lightweight layer to help dry your horse after a bath or keep them clean before a show, are looking for a cover to keep flies away from your horse in the summer, or are looking for a cozy, soft underlayment to keep your horse warm and prevent blanket irritation during the winter, our fleece sheet is perfect! These cotton sheets are even perfect for other equines such as mules and donkeys!</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>DESIGNED WITH YOUR HORSE’S COMFORT IN MIND - this summer sheet was designed to be comfortable to wear long-term and is designed to keep your horse warm in cool weather without overheating.</span></li>
<li><span>HELPS KEEP YOUR HORSE CLEAN - this sheet is lightweight and excellent to use in any season to keep your horse clean before a show or event, or use to help dry your horse and keep them comfortable after a bath.</span></li>
<li><span>PROTECTS AGAINST PESTS - this sheet is great for use as a flu sheet as it helps to keep your horse’s body protected from biting pests such as mosquitoes, flies, and gnats that would otherwise cause sores and irritation.</span></li>
<li><span>CLASSICAL DESIGN WITH PREMIUM FEATURES - this summer sheet features classic designs with a shoulder gusset, front chest buckles, crossed belly surcingles, removable elastic leg straps, and a fleece wither protector.</span></li>
<li><span>GREAT AS A BLANKET UNDERLAYMENT - this sheet is excellent for use during cold weather as an extra layer beneath blankets to help keep your horse warm inside the barn, or in the pasture on chilly days.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>Sizing Information:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This sheet is sized in the same manner that you will size any other horse blanket: by measuring, in inches, from the center of your horse’s chest, to the end of your horse’s rump. If your horse is in-between sizes, we recommend sizing up to the closest available size.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><b>Blanket Care:</b></span></p>
<p><span data-mce-fragment="1">Dried mud, hair, hay, and other debris should be regularly brushed off your blanket. A stiff dandy brush often works best for this. Keeping your blanket clean helps extend its lifespan, as well as help to keep your horse clean and happy. You can also use a damp, soapy rag to remove mud/debris and then wipe your blanket dry. Fleece blankets should only be hand washed and never machine washed. All removable parts should be removed before washing, all velcro straps velcroed together, and your blanket should only be washed in a detergent made for use with horse blankets, or gentle animal-safe cleaners. When washing, use cool water and hand wash gently. Do not use fabric softener with any of our blankets as it will damage their waterproofing and breathing abilities and prevent the blanket from wicking water and sweat off your horse. All of our blankets should be air-dried or line-dried, never put in a dryer. If your blanket becomes nicked or torn, the blanket should immediately be sewn or patched to prevent further damage from occurring.</span></p>
<p><b>Product Information</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blanket Style: Summer Sheet</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Waterproof: No</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breathable: Yes</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weight: Lightweight</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Material: Cotton</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Denier: n/a</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ripstop: No</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tail Cover: No</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wither Protector: Yes</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shoulder Gussets: Yes</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polyfil: 0g</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Inner Lining: Cotton</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Belly Closure: Belly Surgincle</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leg Straps: Removable Elastic</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Colors Available: Hunter Green/Beige Plaid</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sizes Available: 72”, 74”, 76”, 78”, 80”, 82”, and 84”</span></p>
<ul class="product-features-list"></ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>72&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>74&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>76&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>78&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>80&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>82&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>84&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>All Stable Sheets &amp; Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Derby Originals</s:tag>
    <s:tag>FallSeason</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Full Horse Blankets &amp; Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>PLAID</s:tag>
    <s:tag>sheet</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Summer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SummerSale2018</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>72&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-72</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>74&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-74</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>76&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-76</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>78&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-78</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>80&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-80</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>82&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-82</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650512</id>
      <title>84&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>80-8005HB-84</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2245</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
