<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/western-horse-tack.atom"/>
  <title>Tack Wholesale</title>
  <updated>2021-06-01T14:27:29-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tack Wholesale</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6583405084732</id>
    <published>2021-06-01T14:27:29-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-01T14:27:29-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-38-american-pride-bald-eagle-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 38&quot; American Pride Bald Eagle New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Eagle_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Horse_61-3003.png?v=1625672371"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            119.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This unique and luxurious saddle blanket is adorned with the ultimate symbol of American freedom, the mighty Bald Eagle, sitting atop the American flag. This 34 x 38” Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features white stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">BALD EAGLE DESIGN - this flashy saddle blanket features an American bald eagle on either side of the blanket, atop our American flag Stars and Stripes print. This beautiful patriotic design is sure to wow in any competition, event, or parade.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect hand-shaped stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This careful detail gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 34 x 38" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic rectangular rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6583405084732</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">119.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3003-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>6804</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:44:04-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:44:04-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-zara-cactus-solid-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Zara Cactus Solid New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Zara_Cactus_Solid_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3031-BLK.jpg?v=1622146515"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            79.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Zara New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” solid Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. Our blankets also feature brightly colored hand-painted leather cactus accents for added style and flair.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HAND-PAINTED LEATHER ACCENTS - this stunning saddle blanket has a pair of hand-painted leather accents on either side of the back of the blanket. These hand-painted cacti add color and flair that is sure to be noticed.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN SOLID DESIGN - this beautiful solid Western saddle blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Zara blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique solid show blanket features painted leather accents and is available in five different colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid color</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-BLK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-PNK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Dark Purple</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-RED</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Turquoise</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-TRQ</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:43:39-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:43:39-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-kaye-arrow-solid-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Kaye Arrow Solid New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Kaye_Arrow_Solid_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3030-TRQ.jpg?v=1622145946"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Kaye New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” solid Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. Our blankets also feature brightly colored hand-painted leather arrow accents for added style and flair.</span></p>
<ul>
<li>100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HAND-PAINTED LEATHER ACCENTS - this stunning saddle blanket has a pair of hand-painted leather accents on either side of the back of the blanket. These hand-painted arrows add color and flair that is sure to be noticed.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN SOLID DESIGN - this beautiful solid Western saddle blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Kaye blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique solid show blanket features painted leather accents and is available in three different colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid color</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3030-BLK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
      <title>Dark Purple</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3030-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
      <title>Turquoise</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3030-TRQ</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:43:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:43:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-38-livia-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 38&quot; Livia New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Livia_Diamond_Weave_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3021-BLU.jpg?v=1622142649"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            67.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Livia New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 38” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric diamond stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Livia blanket measures 34 x 38” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Turquoise/Blue/Silver/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-BLU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Gold/Purple/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Gold/Red/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-RED</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Gold/Turquoise/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-TRQ</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:42:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:42:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-38-reya-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 38&quot; Reya New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Reya_Diamond_Weave_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3020-BLU.jpg?v=1622222964"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            74.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Reya New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 38” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric diamond stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Reya blanket measures 34 x 38” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Blue/Brown/Turquoise/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-BLU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Pink/Purple/Fuchsia/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-PNK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Purple/Light Purple/Black/Silver/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Tan/Brown/Turquoise/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-TAN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:42:03-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:42:03-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-maisie-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Maisie New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Maisie_Diamond_Weave_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3011-BLU_309f72b5-5e84-498c-82b6-d8a4bd89cbff.jpg?v=1622141750"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Maisie New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric concentric diamond design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Maisie blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Care Instructions</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Black/Turquoise/Blue/Dark Blue/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-BLU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Brown/Tan/Orange/Chocolate/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-BRN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Black/Orange/White/Turquoise/Magenta</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-MGA</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Black/Purple/Turquoise/Silver/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:40:51-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:40:51-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-gemma-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Gemma New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/1Gemma_Diamond_Cross_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Swatch_61-3010-ORG.png?v=1628864164"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Gemma New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric stripe and diamond design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Gemma blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Orange/Cream/Turquoise/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-ORG</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Dark Purple/Light Purple/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Red/Grey/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-RED</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Tan/Turquoise/Gold/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-TAN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967559228</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:39:20-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:39:20-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-american-pride-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; American Pride New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Horse_61-3002.jpg?v=1624542415"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features perfectly shaped embroidered stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect embroidered stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This embroidery gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our American flag blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive patriotic accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 34 x 36" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic rectangular rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967559228</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3002-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1588</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967198780</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:38:10-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:38:10-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-32-x-32-american-pride-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 32&quot; x 32&quot; American Pride New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Horse_61-3001.jpg?v=1624542389"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            59.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 32 x 32” Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features perfectly shaped embroidered stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect embroidered stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This embroidery gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our American flag blanket measures 32 x 32” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive patriotic accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 32 x 32" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic square rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967198780</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">59.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3001-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1247</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572966772796</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:37:34-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:37:34-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-26-x-26-american-pride-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 26&quot; x 26&quot; American Pride New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Pony_61-3000.jpg?v=1624542362"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            49.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 26 x 26” pony-sized Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features perfectly shaped embroidered stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect embroidered stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This embroidery gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our American flag blanket measures 26 x 26” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive patriotic accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 26 x 26" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic square rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Care Instructions</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572966772796</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">49.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3000-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1179</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643063201852</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:35:15-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:35:15-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-leather-western-double-ear-headstall-with-quick-change-bit-ends-and-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Quick Change Bit Leather Western Double Ear Headstall</title>
    <s:type>Headstalls</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/IMG_7980-set1.jpg?v=1620758200"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headstalls<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s latest line of working headstalls has been designed with convenience and ease of use in mind. This new line of browband, slip ear, and double-ear leather headstalls all include new quick-change bit ends. This quick-change design features leather tab ends that are designed to securely hold your bit in place, but can be undone and re-done effortlessly in seconds for removing and changing out bits. These premium leather headstalls are ideal for multi-horse owners! Our headstalls have an adjustable 36-44” bit to bit length and have been designed to fit most horses weighing between 900 and 1250 lbs.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">QUICK CHANGE DESIGN - this Tahoe headstall features leather tab ends that are designed to securely hold your bit in place when in use, but can be undone in seconds in order to change out or remove the bit.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">GREAT FOR MULTI-HORSE OWNERS - if you use different bits for different horses or tasks, or use your tack for multiple horses, this headstall is perfect for you! This ultra-convenient, hassle-free, quick-change design makes swapping bits a breeze.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PREMIUM DOUBLE STITCHED LEATHER - our western double ear headstall is made from high-quality double-stitched leather that will last for many years with proper care and maintenance. This headstall also features stainless steel hardware.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - this headstall is sized to fit most average-to-large sized horses and breeds weighing approx. 900-1250lbs. This headstall has adjustable ear openings and a 36-44” bit to bit measurement.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">AVAILABLE IN TWO COLORS - Tahoe’s line of quick-change headstalls is available in both Medium Oil and Dark Oil: two classic colors that are sure to complement your horse’s color and your other tack.</span></li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>dark oil headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>double ear</s:tag>
    <s:tag>double ear headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>full horse headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>headstall accessories</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstalls &amp; Reins</s:tag>
    <s:tag>leather headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Leather Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>medium oil</s:tag>
    <s:tag>medium oil headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western leather headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>working headstall</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643063201852</id>
      <title>Dark Oil / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2702-DKO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643063201852</id>
      <title>Medium Oil / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2702-MDO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643058876476</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:34:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:34:42-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-leather-western-browband-headstall-with-quick-change-bit-ends-and-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Quick Change Bit Leather Western Browband Headstall</title>
    <s:type>Headstalls</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/IMG_7986-set3.jpg?v=1620757557"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headstalls<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s latest line of working headstalls has been designed with convenience and ease of use in mind. This new line of browband, slip ear, and double-ear leather headstalls all include new quick-change bit ends. This quick-change design features leather tab ends that are designed to securely hold your bit in place, but can be undone and re-done effortlessly in seconds for removing and changing out bits. These premium leather headstalls are ideal for multi-horse owners! Our headstalls have an adjustable 36-44” bit to bit length and have been designed to fit most horses weighing between 900 and 1250 lbs.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">QUICK CHANGE DESIGN - this Tahoe headstall features leather tab ends that are designed to securely hold your bit in place when in use, but can be undone in seconds in order to change out or remove the bit.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">GREAT FOR MULTI-HORSE OWNERS - if you use different bits for different horses or tasks, or use your tack for multiple horses, this headstall is perfect for you! This ultra-convenient, hassle-free, quick-change design makes swapping bits a breeze.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PREMIUM DOUBLE STITCHED LEATHER - our western browband headstall is made from high-quality double-stitched leather that will last for many years with proper care and maintenance. This headstall also features stainless steel hardware.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - this headstall is sized to fit most average-to-large sized horses and breeds weighing approx. 900-1250lbs. This headstall has a 16.5” browband and 36-44” bit to bit measurement.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">AVAILABLE IN TWO COLORS - Tahoe’s line of quick-change headstalls is available in both Medium Oil and Dark Oil: two classic colors that are sure to complement your horse’s color and your other tack.</span></li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>browband headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Browband Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>dark oil</s:tag>
    <s:tag>dark oil headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>full horse headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>headstall accessories</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstalls &amp; Reins</s:tag>
    <s:tag>leather headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Leather Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>medium oil</s:tag>
    <s:tag>medium oil headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western leather headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>working headstall</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643058876476</id>
      <title>Dark Oil / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2700-DKO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643058876476</id>
      <title>Medium Oil / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2700-MDO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6574018822204</id>
    <published>2021-05-13T14:02:29-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-13T14:02:29-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-super-soft-cashmillon-western-saddle-blanket-34-x-36"/>
    <title>Tahoe Super Soft Cashmillon Western Saddle Blanket 34&quot; X 36&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tack Wholesale</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Cashmillon-Saddle-Blanket-Red.jpg?v=1620928934"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tack Wholesale<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            19.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">SIZE AND WEIGHT - this saddle blanket is 36” x 34” and is lightweight at approximately 5 lbs.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">HANDWOVEN - these blankets are hand woven by skilled artisans. Due to the nature of making these by hand, there might be slight differences in each product.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">RED CASHMILON - features comfortable lightweight cashmilon yarn made from acrylic in a vibrant red. This material is extremely flexible soft and fine, perfect for a luxurious ride.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">HAND WASH AND DRY ONLY - to keep this product in the best condition it requires hand washing and hang drying only.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">Tahoe Tack Heavy Duty Red Cashmilon Saddle Blankets are made with soft and lightweight cashmilon yarn made from acrylic. These lightweight red blankets come in size 36” x 34”, and are handwoven by skilled artisans for maximum comfort. To keep this product in good care it requires only hand washing and drying.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6574018822204</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1320-RD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1361</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485414672</id>
    <published>2021-03-03T13:32:46-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-03T13:32:46-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/17-8052"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tacks Gold Cross Silver Conchco 1-1/4&quot; with Screw Back for Western Tack at Wholesale Price</title>
    <s:type>Conchos</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Derby Originals</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/concho_gold_cross_front_17-8051_e93d4f5a-3f98-4879-a4fe-fffb93ca58e9.jpg?v=1583362100"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Derby Originals<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Conchos<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            2.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Silver Plated Concho with Gold Cross Design. Included is the 3/8" diameter screw. These can be used to decorate headstalls, breast collars, and more.<br> <br> Size: 1-1/4"<br><br><br></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>1-1/4&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Derby Originals</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485414672</id>
      <title>1-1/4&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">2.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-8052</s:sku>
      <s:grams>91</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486266064</id>
    <published>2021-03-03T13:32:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-03T13:32:27-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/ll-2256"/>
    <title>Shiny Silver Parachute Western Concho - 1-1/4&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Conchos</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Derby Originals</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Concho_Parachute_Shiny_Front_de670a80-76b1-4c60-96c1-ca6904c9921f.jpg?v=1571609169"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Derby Originals<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Conchos<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            2.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><font size="4" style="font-weight: bold;">Shiny Silver Parachute Concho 1-1/4"</font><font size="4" style="font-weight: bold;"><br>
</font>
<ul><font size="2">
    <li>Round concho features a radial design that resembles an open parachute</li>
    <li>Each concho includes a Chicago screw that is 3/16" long <br>
    </li>
    <li>Can be used to decorate headstalls, breast collars, and other items such as handbags</li>
    </font></ul>
    <font size="4" style="font-weight: bold;"><font size="3" style="font-weight: bold;">Size: 1-1/4" diameter<br>
    Color: Shiny Silver </font><font size="3"><br>
    </font><font size="3" style="font-weight: bold;"><br>
    </font></font><font size="4"><font size="3"><font size="2">Retail Price: $8.95</font></font></font><font size="4" style="font-weight: bold;"><font size="3" style="font-weight: bold;"><font size="2"><br>
    <span style="font-weight: bold;">Our Wholesale Price: <span style="color: rgb(255, 0, 0);">$3.95</span></span></font> </font></font></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Derby Originals</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486266064</id>
      <title>Shiny Silver</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">2.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>LL-2256</s:sku>
      <s:grams>113</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492948240</id>
    <published>2020-11-30T08:53:56-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-30T08:53:56-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/20-4487-a"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Angled Engraved Knee Relief Western Show Stirrups</title>
    <s:type>Stirrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/766.jpg?v=1574548578"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Stirrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            34.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s engraved angled wetern stirrups were designed to enhance the overall appearance of a western rider in the show and gymkhana ring, while providing knee and hip pain relief that riders often experience. Although these stirrups are beautifully hand engraved, they are not bulky or overly flashy in a way that will distract from the riders performance. These stirrups are versatile and can be used in a variety of western events including western pleasure, horsemanship, trail, gymkhana barrel racing, and everyday riding on the trails. They simply add the right amount of elegance and comfort to your existing tack set. These stirrups only feature the engraved design on one side of each stirrup and are sold in pairs. The color/shade of the leather pieces on these stirrups may very slightly from lot to lot.  </span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p style="display: inline !important;"><span>DESIGNED WITH YOUR COMFORT IN MIND - these feature an offset design that aids in preventing knee and hip pain while riding that allows you to ride for longer periods of time and remain more comfortable than traditional stirrups.</span></p>
</li>
<li><span>HAND ENGRAVED DESIGN - these stirrups feature beautiful hand engraving that give the extra detail needed to set you apart in the show arena. Due to the fact that each stirrup is individually hand engraved, the engravings may vary slightly between each stirrup, but overall have the same engraving pattern.</span></li>
<li><span>IN THE SHOW RING - These stirrups are beautiful in our out of the show ring. Weather you are showing or riding on the trails, these stirrups are eye catching and make any saddle stand out from the rest.</span></li>
<li><span>STURDY ALUMINUM CONSTRUCTION - Made of strong, hand-engraved, solid aluminum that will never rust. These also feature rubber foot grips to help the riders foot stay in place throughout the entire ride.</span></li>
<li><span>AVAILABLE IN ADULT SIZE - available in Adult (5”) size to accommodate most riders. Our stirrups are universally sized to fit any western saddle.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul class="product-features-list"></ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>accessories</s:tag>
    <s:tag>angled stirrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>engraved</s:tag>
    <s:tag>knee pain stirrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>knee relief</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SHOW</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show stirrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>silver engraved</s:tag>
    <s:tag>silver engraved stirrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>stirrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western stirrups</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492948240</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>20-4487AD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1347</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643045998652</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T16:21:05-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T16:21:05-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-silver-texas-star-leather-western-ladies-spur-straps-with-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Silver Texas Star Show Spotted Leather Western Ladies Spur Straps</title>
    <s:type>Western Spurs &amp; Straps</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Western_Leather_Spur_Straps_Ladies_Texas_Star_17-2615.jpg?v=1605216038"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Western Spurs &amp; Straps<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            21.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star Show Spotted Leather Western Ladies Spur Straps is an attractive new Medium Oil leather pair of ladies spur straps that are a part of the Texas Star series. These new leather spur straps feature flashy engraved 1” Texas Star conchos placed in the center of each of the spur straps, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the spur straps. These spur straps were designed for women and will fit most boot sizes. Our spur straps are adjustable from 8.5” to 10” long, and are 2.5” wide at the widest point, tapering down to ⅝”. Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star collection also includes matching tack pieces such as a browband headstall, slip ear headstall, noseband, split reins, and breast collar. </span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PART OF THE TEXAS STAR COLLECTION - this pair of spur straps is part of Tahoe Tack’s new Texas Star collection, which is composed of matching Medium Oil leather tack pieces featuring Texas Star conchos and stainless steel show spots.</span></li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST WOMEN - our ladies spur straps are “one size fits all” and are designed to fit most boots. Our spur straps </span><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">are adjustable from 8.5” to 10” long, and are 2.5” wide at the widest point, tapering down to ⅝”. </span>
</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">SPOTTED TEXAS STAR DESIGN - these new leather spur straps feature flashy engraved 1” Texas Star conchos placed in the center of each of the spur straps, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the spur straps. </span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">FITS ALL SPURS - our universal ladies spur straps are designed to fit all western spurs.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">ONE YEAR WARRANTY - this product comes with a one-year limited manufacturer’s warranty that protects against quality issues and defects. To register your product, visit the manufacturer Derby Originals' website.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">End to End: 8.5” - 10”</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Width: Tapers from 2.5” to ⅝”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643045998652</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">21.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2615-MDO-LDY</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643045113916</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T15:41:08-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T15:41:08-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-silver-texas-star-leather-western-breast-collar-with-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Silver Texas Star Show Spotted Leather Western Horse Breast Collar</title>
    <s:type>Breast Collars</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Texas_Silver_Star_Western_Tack_Breast_Collar_Medium_Oil_Main_17-2614.png?v=1605197367"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Breast Collars<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            62.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star Show Spotted Leather Western Horse Breast Collar is an attractive new Medium Oil leather breast collar that is a part of the Texas Star series. This new leather breast collar features a flashy engraved 1.25” Texas Star concho placed in the center of the breast collar, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the body of the breast collar. This breast collar was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a total length of 53” - 59”, and measures 29” - 31” from the center of the breast collar to the snap. Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star collection also includes matching tack pieces such as a browband headstall, slip ear headstall, noseband, split reins, and spur straps.</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PART OF THE TEXAS STAR COLLECTION - this breast collar is part of Tahoe Tack’s new Texas Star collection, which is composed of matching Medium Oil leather tack pieces featuring Texas Star conchos and stainless steel show spots.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - this breast collar was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a total length of 53” - 59”, and measures 29” - 31” from the center of the breast collar to the snap.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">SPOTTED TEXAS STAR DESIGN - this breast collar features a flashy engraved 1.25” Texas Star concho in the center of the breast collar, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire breast collar.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">CENTER D-RING ACCOMMODATES TIE DOWN - this breast collar has a D-ring placed in the center of the breast collar to allow for the easy addition and removal of a tie down.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">ONE YEAR WARRANTY - this product comes with a one-year limited manufacturer’s warranty that protects against quality issues and defects. To register your product, visit the manufacturer Derby Originals' website.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Total Length: 53” - 59”</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">To the Girth: 29” - 31</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Width: Tapers from 1 ¼” to ⅝”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>breast collar</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Breast Collars</s:tag>
    <s:tag>leather breast collar</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Leather Breast Collars</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643045113916</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">62.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2614-MDO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>726</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643038658620</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T11:08:18-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:08:18-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-silver-texas-star-leather-western-noseband-with-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Silver Texas Star Padded Leather Western Horse Noseband</title>
    <s:type>Nosebands and Accessories</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Texas_Silver_Star_Western_Tack_Padded_Noseband_Medium_Oil_Detail_17-2612.png?v=1605197327"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Nosebands and Accessories<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            29.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star Padded Leather Western Horse Noseband is an attractive new Medium Oil leather noseband that is a part of the Texas Star series. This new noseband features a flashy engraved 1” Texas Star concho on either side of the noseband, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire nose of the noseband. This noseband was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 33” noseband, and 37” - 43” crown. Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star collection also includes matching tack pieces such as a browband headstall, slip ear headstall, split reins, breast collar, and spur straps.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PART OF THE TEXAS STAR COLLECTION - this noseband is part of Tahoe Tack’s new Texas Star collection, which is composed of matching Medium Oil leather tack pieces featuring Texas Star conchos and stainless steel show spots.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - this noseband was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 33” noseband, and 37” - 43” crown.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">SPOTTED TEXAS STAR DESIGN - this noseband features flashy engraved 1” Texas Star conchos on either side of the nose, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire nose of the noseband.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PADDED NOSEBAND FOR INCREASED COMFORT - our nosebands feature soft leather padding on the underside of the noseband to increase your horse’s comfort during use and promote a healthy fur coat.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">ONE YEAR WARRANTY - this product comes with a one-year limited manufacturer’s warranty that protects against quality issues and defects. To register your product, visit the manufacturer Derby Originals' website.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Noseband: 33”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crown: 37” - 43”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>noseband</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643038658620</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2612-MDO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>295</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643038429244</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T11:07:37-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:07:37-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-silver-texas-star-leather-western-slip-ear-headstall-with-buckle-bit-ends-and-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Silver Texas Star Leather Western Horse Slip Ear Headstall with Buckle Bit Ends</title>
    <s:type>Headstalls</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Texas_Silver_Star_Western_Tack_Slip_Ear_Headstall_Medium_Oil_Main_17-2611.png?v=1605197270"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headstalls<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            34.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack Silver Texas Star Leather Western Horse Slip Ear Headstall with Buckle Bit Ends is an attractive new Medium Oil leather headstall that is a part of the Texas Star series. This new slip ear headstall features a flashy engraved 1” Texas Star concho on the side of the slip ear, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire crown and cheeks of the headstall. This headstall was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 41” - 48” bit to bit length, and a sliding slip ear. Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star collection also includes matching tack pieces such as a browband headstall, noseband, split reins, breast collar, and spur straps.</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PART OF THE TEXAS STAR COLLECTION - this headstall is part of Tahoe Tack’s new Texas Star collection, which is composed of matching Medium Oil leather tack pieces featuring Texas Star conchos and stainless steel show spots.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - this headstall was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 41” - 48” bit to bit length, and a sliding slip ear.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">SPOTTED TEXAS STAR DESIGN - this headstall features a flashy engraved 1” Texas Star concho on the side of the slip ear, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire crown and cheeks of the headstall.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">CONVENIENT BUCKLE BIT ENDS - this headstall features buckle bit ends which makes adjusting or changing your bit a breeze compared to traditional cumbersome leather ties, Conway buckles, or Chicago screws.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">ONE YEAR WARRANTY - this product comes with a one-year limited manufacturer’s warranty that protects against quality issues and defects. To register your product, visit the manufacturer Derby Originals' website.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Bit to Bit: 41” - 48”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643038429244</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2611-MDO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>318</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643038199868</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T11:06:43-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:06:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-silver-texas-star-leather-western-browband-headstall-with-buckle-bit-ends-and-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Silver Texas Star Leather Western Horse Browband Headstall with Buckle Bit Ends</title>
    <s:type>Headstalls</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Texas_Silver_Star_Western_Tack_Browband_Headstall_Medium_Oil_Main_17-2610.png?v=1605197216"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headstalls<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            44.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star Leather Western Horse Browband Headstall with Buckle Bit Ends is an attractive new Medium Oil leather headstall that is a part of the Texas Star series. This new browband headstall features flashy engraved 1.25” Texas Star conchos on either side of the browband, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire browband, crown, and cheeks of the headstall. This headstall was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 16” browband, 36” - 44” bit to bit length, and 40” - 45” throatlatch. Tahoe Tack’s Silver Texas Star collection also includes matching tack pieces such as a slip ear headstall, noseband, split reins, breast collar, and spur straps.</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PART OF THE TEXAS STAR COLLECTION - this headstall is part of Tahoe Tack’s new Texas Star collection, which is composed of matching Medium Oil leather tack pieces featuring Texas Star conchos and stainless steel show spots.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - this headstall was designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 16” browband, 36” - 44” bit to bit length, and 40” - 45” throatlatch.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">SPOTTED TEXAS STAR DESIGN - this headstall features flashy engraved 1.25” Texas Star conchos on either side of the browband, as well as attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire browband, crown, and cheeks of the headstall.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">CONVENIENT BUCKLE BIT ENDS - this headstall features buckle bit ends which makes adjusting or changing your bit a breeze compared to traditional cumbersome leather ties, Conway buckles, or Chicago screws.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">ONE YEAR WARRANTY - this product comes with a one-year limited manufacturer’s warranty that protects against quality issues and defects. To register your product, visit the manufacturer Derby Originals' website.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Browband: 16”</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Bit to Bit: 36” - 44”</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Throatlatch: 40” - 45”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Leather Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643038199868</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">44.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-2610-MDO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643021652028</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T13:33:22-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-10T13:33:22-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-starry-night-leather-western-noseband-with-one-year-warranty"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Starry Night Black Padded Leather Western Horse Noseband</title>
    <s:type>Nosebands and Accessories</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/1Leather_Western_Noseband_Matching_Spotted_Black_Main_17-1737.png?v=1605197114"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Nosebands and Accessories<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            32.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack's Starry Night Padded Leather Western Noseband for Horses is the latest installment in our Starry Night tack series. This series features attractive black leather tack with double-stitching and stainless steel show spotting adornments that are ideal for everything from everyday riding to the show ring. Our Starry Night noseband is designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and has a 33” noseband and 37” - 43” crown. These nosebands are easy to adjust to fit your horse. Be sure to check out Tahoe Tack's matching Starry Night headstall and breast collar!</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - these nosebands are designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and have a 33” noseband, and 37” - 43” crown.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PREMIUM LEATHER CONSTRUCTION - these nylon Western nosebands are made from leather, which is durable and long-lasting with proper care, easy to maintain, and comfortable for your horse to wear.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PADDED NOSEBAND FOR INCREASED COMFORT - our nosebands feature soft leather padding on the underside of the noseband to increase your horse’s comfort during use and promote a healthy fur coat.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">STAINLESS STEEL SHOW SPOTTING - our Starry Night noseband features a line of flashy and attractive stainless steel show spots covering the entire nose, which adds flair and style.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED FOR USE WITH A TIE-DOWN - this Western noseband has been designed for use with a tie down and features a sturdy nickel-plated o-ring at the bottom of the noseband that is designed to universally fit any tie down.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Noseband: 33”</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Crown: 37” - 43”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>black leather noseband</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643021652028</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">32.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1737-BLK-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>680</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T12:58:04-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-10T12:58:04-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-overlay-printed-nylon-western-noseband"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Patterned Nylon Padded Western Noseband for Horses Available in Six Colors</title>
    <s:type>Nosebands and Accessories</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/1Nylon_Western_Noseband_Overlay_Pattern_Blue_Aztec_Swatch_17-1701.png?v=1605196977"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Nosebands and Accessories<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            19.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack's Patterned Nylon Padded Western Noseband for Horses was designed to offer a more modern, attractive, and high-quality nylon noseband option compared to your basic, plain, nylon nosebands that are flimsy and unattractive. Our nosebands are available in six attractive patterns so that you can find the option that best suits you and your horse. Our line of patterned nosebands is designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and have a 28” noseband, and 38” - 43” crown. These nosebands are easy to adjust to fit your horse. Be sure to check out Tahoe Tack's matching nylon overlay browband headstalls, slip ear headstalls, halters. bucket straps, and more!</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - these nosebands are designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and have a 28” noseband and 38” - 43” crown.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PREMIUM NYLON CONSTRUCTION - these nylon Western nosebands are made from heavy-duty nylon webbing, which is durable, long-lasting, easy to care for, comfortable for your horse to wear, and resistant to rips or tears.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PADDED NOSEBAND FOR INCREASED COMFORT - our nylon nosebands feature soft neoprene padding on the underside of the noseband to increase your horse’s comfort during use and promote a healthy fur coat.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">FEATURES ATTRACTIVE OVERLAY PRINT - our unique nosebands feature modern and stylish printed designs such as Aztec, Chevron, Paisley, and more on the top of the noseband, which lets them stand out compared to regular plain nylon nosebands.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">AVAILABLE IN SIX ATTRACTIVE COLORS - our nosebands are available in Blue Aztec on Black nylon, Red Aztec on Red nylon, Blue Chevron on Hurricane Blue nylon, Paisley on Grey nylon, Geometric on Hurricane Blue nylon, and Grey Floral on Hot Pink nylon.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Noseband: 28”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crown: 38” - 43”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>noseband</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
      <title>Blue Aztec / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1701-AZC-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
      <title>Grey Floral / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1701-GRF-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
      <title>Paisley / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1701-PAS-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
      <title>Blue Chevron / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1701-BLC-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
      <title>Geometric / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1701-GEO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643020243004</id>
      <title>Red Aztec / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1701-RAZ-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
    <published>2020-11-09T16:58:50-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-09T16:58:50-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-nylon-western-browband-headstall-with-overlay"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Patterned Double Layer Nylon Western Browband Headstalls for Horses Available in 6 Colors</title>
    <s:type>Headstalls</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/1Nylon_Western_Browband-Headstall_Overlay_Pattern_Blue_Aztec_Swatch_17-1700.png?v=1605196960"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headstalls<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            24.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack's Patterned Double Layer Nylon Western Browband Headstalls for Horses were designed to offer a more modern, attractive, and high-quality nylon headstall option compared to your basic, plain, single-layered nylon headstalls that are flimsy and unattractive. Our headstalls are available in six attractive patterns so that you can find the option that best suits you and your horse. Our line of patterned headstalls is designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and have a 16” browband, 40”-44” throatlatch, and 39”-47” bit to bit length. These headstalls are easy to adjust on the throatlatch and cheeks, and have nickel-plated Conway buckle ends to make changing bits easier and hassle-free. Be sure to check out Tahoe Tack's matching nylon overlay slip ear headstalls, nosebands, halters. bucket straps, and more!</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">DESIGNED TO FIT MOST HORSES - these headstalls are designed to fit most horses weighing between 1,000-1,250 lbs and have a 16” browband, 40”-44” throatlatch, and 39”-47” bit to bit length.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PREMIUM DOUBLE-LAYERED CONSTRUCTION - these nylon Western headstalls are made from heavy-duty double-layered nylon webbing, which is durable, long-lasting, easy to care for, comfortable for your horse to wear, and resistant to rips or tears.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PADDED BROWBAND FOR INCREASED COMFORT - our nylon browband headstalls feature soft neoprene padding on the underside of the browband to increase your horse’s comfort during use and promote a healthy fur coat.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">FEATURES ATTRACTIVE OVERLAY PRINT - our unique headstalls feature modern and stylish printed designs such as Aztec, Chevron, Paisley, and more on the browband and cheeks of the headstall, which lets them stand out compared to regular plain nylon headstalls.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">AVAILABLE IN SIX ATTRACTIVE COLORS - our headstalls are available in Blue Aztec on Black nylon, Red Aztec on Red nylon, Blue Chevron on Hurricane Blue nylon, Paisley on Grey nylon, Geometric on Hurricane Blue nylon, and Grey Floral on Hot Pink nylon.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Measurements:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Browband: 16”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bit to Bit: 39” - 47”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Throatlatch: 40” - 44”</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Nylon Headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Nylon Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
      <title>Blue Aztec / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1700-AZC-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
      <title>Blue Chevron / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1700-BLC-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
      <title>Geometric / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1700-GEO-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
      <title>Grey Floral / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1700-GRF-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
      <title>Paisley / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1700-PAS-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4643017097276</id>
      <title>Red Aztec / Full/Average</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1700-RAZ-FUL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4671194267708</id>
    <published>2020-11-03T16:20:33-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-03T16:20:33-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-zebra-print-overlay-nylon-western-browband-headstall-with-matching-reins"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Zebra Print Overlay Nylon Western Browband Headstall with Matching Reins</title>
    <s:type>Headstalls</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Tahoe-Zebra-Print-Padded-Headstall-RNS.jpg?v=1604438419"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headstalls<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            12.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">Tahoe Tack’s “Pleasure Rider” series is composed of beautiful leather and nylon headstalls that are made with trail riding and other similar equestrian activities in mind. These halters are beautiful and high-quality, with durable, more plain designs that are suited to trail rides and pleasure riding. This series was designed with quality in mind and features classic western designs.</span></p>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<ul data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1">QUALITY CONSTRUCTION - this headstall was designed by Tahoe Tack, a fine maker of quality western tack for over 20 years. It features durable hardware and high-quality leather that is designed to last many years with proper care.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">HORSE SIZE AVAILABLE - this headstall is available in Full Horse sizing to accommodate most average sized equines.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">MULTIPLE COLORS AVAILABLE - this headstall is available in two nylon colors: White/Black Zebra Print, and Pink/Black Zebra Print.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">MATCHING SPLIT REINS - this browband includes a pair of matching split reins that measure 83” long.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">CHICAGO SCREW STYLE - this headstall features classic Chicago screw style ends, which makes adding or switching bits out as easy as can be.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Nylon Headstall</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Nylon Headstalls</s:tag>
    <s:tag>zebra print</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4671194267708</id>
      <title>Full Horse / White Zebra</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>17-1705BK-F</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
