<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/western-saddle-blankets-pads.atom"/>
  <title>Tack Wholesale</title>
  <updated>2021-06-01T14:27:29-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tack Wholesale</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6583405084732</id>
    <published>2021-06-01T14:27:29-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-01T14:27:29-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-38-american-pride-bald-eagle-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 38&quot; American Pride Bald Eagle New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Eagle_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Horse_61-3003.png?v=1625672371"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            119.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This unique and luxurious saddle blanket is adorned with the ultimate symbol of American freedom, the mighty Bald Eagle, sitting atop the American flag. This 34 x 38” Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features white stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">BALD EAGLE DESIGN - this flashy saddle blanket features an American bald eagle on either side of the blanket, atop our American flag Stars and Stripes print. This beautiful patriotic design is sure to wow in any competition, event, or parade.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect hand-shaped stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This careful detail gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 34 x 38" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic rectangular rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6583405084732</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">119.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3003-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>6804</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:44:04-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:44:04-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-zara-cactus-solid-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Zara Cactus Solid New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Zara_Cactus_Solid_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3031-BLK.jpg?v=1622146515"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            79.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Zara New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” solid Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. Our blankets also feature brightly colored hand-painted leather cactus accents for added style and flair.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HAND-PAINTED LEATHER ACCENTS - this stunning saddle blanket has a pair of hand-painted leather accents on either side of the back of the blanket. These hand-painted cacti add color and flair that is sure to be noticed.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN SOLID DESIGN - this beautiful solid Western saddle blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Zara blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique solid show blanket features painted leather accents and is available in five different colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid color</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-BLK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-PNK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Dark Purple</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-RED</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986892348</id>
      <title>Turquoise</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3031-TRQ</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:43:39-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:43:39-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-kaye-arrow-solid-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Kaye Arrow Solid New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Kaye_Arrow_Solid_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3030-TRQ.jpg?v=1622145946"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Kaye New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” solid Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. Our blankets also feature brightly colored hand-painted leather arrow accents for added style and flair.</span></p>
<ul>
<li>100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HAND-PAINTED LEATHER ACCENTS - this stunning saddle blanket has a pair of hand-painted leather accents on either side of the back of the blanket. These hand-painted arrows add color and flair that is sure to be noticed.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN SOLID DESIGN - this beautiful solid Western saddle blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Kaye blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique solid show blanket features painted leather accents and is available in three different colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid color</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3030-BLK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
      <title>Dark Purple</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3030-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572986269756</id>
      <title>Turquoise</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3030-TRQ</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:43:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:43:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-38-livia-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 38&quot; Livia New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Livia_Diamond_Weave_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3021-BLU.jpg?v=1622142649"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            67.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Livia New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 38” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric diamond stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Livia blanket measures 34 x 38” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Turquoise/Blue/Silver/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-BLU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Gold/Purple/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Gold/Red/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-RED</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970770492</id>
      <title>Black/Gold/Turquoise/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">67.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3021-TRQ</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4536</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:42:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:42:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-38-reya-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 38&quot; Reya New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Reya_Diamond_Weave_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3020-BLU.jpg?v=1622222964"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            74.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Reya New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 38” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric diamond stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Reya blanket measures 34 x 38” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Blue/Brown/Turquoise/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-BLU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Pink/Purple/Fuchsia/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-PNK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Purple/Light Purple/Black/Silver/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572970442812</id>
      <title>Tan/Brown/Turquoise/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">74.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3020-TAN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3629</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:42:03-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:42:03-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-maisie-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Maisie New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Maisie_Diamond_Weave_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_61-3011-BLU_309f72b5-5e84-498c-82b6-d8a4bd89cbff.jpg?v=1622141750"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Maisie New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric concentric diamond design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Maisie blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<br data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Care Instructions</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Black/Turquoise/Blue/Dark Blue/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-BLU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Brown/Tan/Orange/Chocolate/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-BRN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Black/Orange/White/Turquoise/Magenta</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-MGA</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572968280124</id>
      <title>Black/Purple/Turquoise/Silver/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3011-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:40:51-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:40:51-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-gemma-new-zealand-wool-western-show-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; Gemma New Zealand Wool Western Show Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/1Gemma_Diamond_Cross_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Swatch_61-3010-ORG.png?v=1628864164"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step into the show ring with pride with this stunning Gemma New Zealand Wool Western Show Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” Western show saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. Unlike inferior show blankets, ours have matching wear leathers for added durability and lifespan. This brightly colored geometric diamond design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features attractive and bright colors that are sure to complement your show outfit in the ring.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% NEW ZEALAND WOOL - our premium show blanket is made from pure New Zealand Wool. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking for increased comfort. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATTERNED DESIGN - this beautiful geometric stripe and diamond design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A SHOW WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features a mix of bright attractive colors on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">STAND OUT IN THE RING - this unique show blanket features an attractive geometric design available in four different sets of colors to best match your horse’s coat along with your tack and show attire. This blanket is sure to help you wow the judges!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our Gemma blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive show accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Geometric</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pattern</s:tag>
    <s:tag>print</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>show pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Orange/Cream/Turquoise/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-ORG</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Dark Purple/Light Purple/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Red/Grey/Tan/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-RED</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967723068</id>
      <title>Black/Tan/Turquoise/Gold/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3010-TAN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1814</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967559228</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:39:20-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:39:20-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-34-x-36-american-pride-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 34&quot; x 36&quot; American Pride New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Horse_61-3002.jpg?v=1624542415"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 34 x 36” Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features perfectly shaped embroidered stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect embroidered stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This embroidery gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our American flag blanket measures 34 x 36” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive patriotic accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 34 x 36" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic rectangular rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967559228</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3002-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1588</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967198780</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:38:10-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:38:10-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-32-x-32-american-pride-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 32&quot; x 32&quot; American Pride New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Horse_61-3001.jpg?v=1624542389"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            59.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 32 x 32” Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features perfectly shaped embroidered stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect embroidered stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This embroidery gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our American flag blanket measures 32 x 32” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive patriotic accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 32 x 32" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic square rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<p><b>Care Instructions</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572967198780</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">59.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3001-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1247</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572966772796</id>
    <published>2021-05-19T16:37:34-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-19T16:37:34-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-26-x-26-american-pride-new-zealand-wool-western-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack 26&quot; x 26&quot; American Pride New Zealand Wool Western Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Patriotic_American_Flag_Western_Saddle_Pad_Blanket_Pony_61-3000.jpg?v=1624542362"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            49.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">Show your American Pride with this stunning Stars and Stripes Series Patriotic Blanket by Tahoe Tack. This 26 x 26” pony-sized Western saddle blanket is made from 100% pure New Zealand Wool, renowned for its luxurious feel, quality, and strength. This wool is breathable and moisture-wicking which helps to increase your horse's comfort by preventing overheating and excess sweating. Our tightly woven designs have been constructed to last for many years to come with proper care. This patriotic American flag design saddle blanket is hand-woven and features perfectly shaped embroidered stars on a blue background, paired with red and white alternating stripes. Our beautiful patriotic blanket is sure to look stunning in any parade, event, or contest you use it in.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN PATRIOTIC DESIGN - this beautiful patriotic stars and stripe design blanket is completely hand-woven and dyed by skilled craftsmen for supreme durability and beauty that will last many years with proper care.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">A PARADE WORTHY PAD - our saddle blanket was meticulously designed in the USA and features embroidered stars on top of hand-woven tight-knit 100% New Zealand Wool for a beautiful finish that is sure to look stunning in parades, events, and contests.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">PERFECTLY SHAPED STARS - this premium saddle blanket features perfect embroidered stars, unlike other inferior blankets that have misshapen hand-woven stars. This embroidery gives this blanket a smoother and cleaner finish compared to others.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">IDEAL FOR LAYERING - our American flag blanket measures 26 x 26” and is designed to be used on top of your regular saddle pad as a colorful and attractive patriotic accessory. This blanket is a great way to add style without adding excess bulk.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">MAKES A STUNNING RUG - this saddle blanket isn't just for horses, but is also great for your home! This beautiful 26 x 26" stars and stripes blanket can be laid flat to turn it into an attractive hand-woven patriotic square rug.</span></li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><b data-mce-fragment="1">Care Instructions</b></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-mce-fragment="1" data-mce-style="font-weight: 400;">This Western saddle blanket should be regularly cleaned and maintained in order to ensure your horse's comfort and prolong the lifespan of the blanket. Never machine wash or dry your blanket. Instead, you should regularly clean it of dirt and fur by gently brushing it with a soft brush. Next, use a vacuum hose to remove any remaining debris from your blanket. Once your blanket is mostly clean, you can wash it with lukewarm to cold water and Woolite™ or specialty saddle pad cleaner to remove any further dirt and sweat. It's important that, after washing, you store your blanket properly on a rack without any tack on top of it to allow it to maintain its shape and thoroughly dry out.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>american flag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>new zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Blankets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6572966772796</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">49.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-3000-PAT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1179</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6574018822204</id>
    <published>2021-05-13T14:02:29-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-05-13T14:02:29-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-super-soft-cashmillon-western-saddle-blanket-34-x-36"/>
    <title>Tahoe Super Soft Cashmillon Western Saddle Blanket 34&quot; X 36&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tack Wholesale</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Cashmillon-Saddle-Blanket-Red.jpg?v=1620928934"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tack Wholesale<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            19.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">SIZE AND WEIGHT - this saddle blanket is 36” x 34” and is lightweight at approximately 5 lbs.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">HANDWOVEN - these blankets are hand woven by skilled artisans. Due to the nature of making these by hand, there might be slight differences in each product.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">RED CASHMILON - features comfortable lightweight cashmilon yarn made from acrylic in a vibrant red. This material is extremely flexible soft and fine, perfect for a luxurious ride.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">HAND WASH AND DRY ONLY - to keep this product in the best condition it requires hand washing and hang drying only.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">Tahoe Tack Heavy Duty Red Cashmilon Saddle Blankets are made with soft and lightweight cashmilon yarn made from acrylic. These lightweight red blankets come in size 36” x 34”, and are handwoven by skilled artisans for maximum comfort. To keep this product in good care it requires only hand washing and drying.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/6574018822204</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1320-RD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1361</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4737631092796</id>
    <published>2021-02-23T11:34:42-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-23T11:34:42-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-shock-absorbing-blocked-new-zealand-wool-saddle-pad"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Heavy-Duty Shock-Absorbing Blocked New Zealand Wool Saddle Pad 36&quot; x 34&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Pads</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tack Wholesale</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Saddle_Pad_Blocked_Colors-2021.jpg?v=1614097491"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tack Wholesale<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Pads<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong>This pad is a warehouse find. It may have minor imperfections due to storage. It has not been used. No returns are allowed.</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">SIZE AND WEIGHT - this saddle pad is 36” x 34” and is heavyweight.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">NEW ZEALAND WOOL - 100% of the topper is made from pure New Zealand wool. Wool from New Zealand is known to be stronger, thicker, and whiter. This allows the color after dying to be clean and clearer than darker wools, and the wool fibers are strong and durable.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">EXTRA COMFORT AND ABSORBS SHOCK - features thick wool felt in the center to absorb shock and contours to horse's back to keep from shifting. The added New Zealand wool topper is extra comfort and support to an already very thick saddle pad.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">ULTRA-SOFT SYNTHETIC FLEECE LINING - is perfect for the horse and helps wick away moisture.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">HAND WASH AND DRY ONLY - to keep this product in the best condition it requires hand washing and hang drying only.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">WEAR LEATHERS - this pad features wear leathers which are made of quality leather for increased durability. This prevents the pad from fraying and ensures long-lasting use.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">This saddle pad is composed of 100% New Zealand Wool topper, with a wool felt inner layer and thick synthetic fleece against the horse. Wear leathers are also in place to prevent pad fraying and to ensure long-lasting use. This product is perfect for western riders at any equine event! Each saddle pad is patterned. To keep this product in good care it requires only hand washing and drying. The size of this pad is 36” x 34” and remarkably thick with padding. This product is designed to absorb shock and bring the rider and the horse extra comfort.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>horse saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4737631092796</id>
      <title>Sage Green/Rust/Sand</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1322-SG/RT/SD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5443</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4737631092796</id>
      <title>Blue/Cream/Navy</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1322-BL/CR/NY</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5443</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4737631092796</id>
      <title>Sand/Coral/Espresso</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1322-SD/CL/ES</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5443</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4638315544636</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T17:11:40-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T17:11:40-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-pony-sized-heavy-duty-shock-absorbing-fleece-backed-new-zealand-wool-saddle-pad-24-x-24"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Pony Sized Heavy-Duty Shock-Absorbing Fleece Backed New Zealand Wool Saddle Pad  24&quot; x 24&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Pads</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tack Wholesale</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Saddle_Pad_Pony_Colors.v2.v2.jpg?v=1599685901"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tack Wholesale<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Pads<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            34.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">SIZE - this pony saddle pad is 24” x 24”.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">NEW ZEALAND WOOL - 100% of the topper is made from pure New Zealand wool. Wool from New Zealand is known to be stronger, thicker, and whiter. This allows the color after dying to be clean and clearer than darker wools, and the wool fibers are strong and durable.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">EXTRA COMFORT AND ABSORBS SHOCK - features thick wool felt in the center to absorb shock and contours to pony’s back to keep from shifting. The added New Zealand wool topper is extra comfort and support to an already very thick saddle pad.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">ULTRA-SOFT SYNTHETIC FLEECE LINING - is perfect for the pony and helps wick away moisture.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">VARIOUS COLORS - each saddle pad is patterned and contains three colors. There are 2 variations one in </span><span data-mce-fragment="1">Royal/Blue/Pink, and the other in Black/Orange/Yellow.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">HANDWASH AND DRY ONLY - to keep this product in the best condition it requires hand washing and hang drying only.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">WEAR LEATHERS - this pad features wear leathers which are made of quality leather for increased durability. This prevents the pad from fraying and ensures long-lasting use.</span></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">This 24” x 24” pony saddle pad is composed of 100% New Zealand Wool topper, with a wool felt inner layer and thick synthetic fleece against the pony. Wear leathers are also in place to prevent pad fraying and to ensure long-lasting use. Each saddle pad is patterned and contains three colors. There are 2 variations one in Royal/Blue/Pink, and the other in Black/Orange/Yellow. To keep this product in good care it requires only hand washing and drying. This product is designed to absorb shock and bring the rider and the horse extra comfort.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>mini saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pony saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4638315544636</id>
      <title>Black/Orange/Yellow</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1324-BK/OR/YW</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2722</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
    <published>2020-08-24T09:54:50-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-08-24T09:54:50-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/61-1002"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Navajo Print Handwoven Acrylic Saddle Blanket 30&quot; x 30&quot; CLOSEOUT</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Saddle_Blanket_Navajo_61-1002.v2.v2_cd7e974e-c20e-4838-a0bc-773a2544a166.jpg?v=1571609187"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            12.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p style="text-align: center;">Tightly handwoven Navajo design made with high-quality acrylic material. The square blanket may be folded along length or width. Size: 30" x 30"  Hand wash and hang dry only. Navajo saddle blankets can also be used as rugs, seat covers, or even wall decor at home!<br><br></p>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>Measurements: 30" x 30"</li>
<li>Traditional Navajo design handwoven by highly skilled craftsmen  </li>
<li>Made with quality acrylic, Tightly woven and durable weave</li>
<li>Hand wash and hang dry only</li>
<li>Also can be used as home decoration!</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Fuchsia</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Green</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Navy</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Red</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pad Summer Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
      <title>Green</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1002GR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
      <title>Fuchsia</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1002PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1002RD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1002BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
      <title>Tan</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1002TN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492745680</id>
      <title>Navy</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1002NV</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4616503296060</id>
    <published>2020-08-12T14:08:51-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-08-12T14:08:51-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-contoured-comfort-pressure-relieving-pure-new-zealand-wool-36x34-saddle-blanket"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Contoured Comfort Pressure-Relieving Pure New Zealand Wool 36x34&quot; Saddle Blanket</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/contourgroup.v5.v2.jpg?v=1597255731"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            37.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><span>This saddle blanket is designed for comfort. Ideal for high withered horses, as the gentle contour helps prevent additional pressure on the spine. Shaped with no center seam. Perfect for western riders. 36" spine length x 34"</span><br><br>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>100% New Zealand Wool. Soft yet durable and allows the horse's skin to breathe</li>
<li>Contoured shape with no seam for a comfortable fit</li>
<li>Designed to fit the horses' back perfectly</li>
<li>Each blanket is approximately 3.65 lbs</li>
<li>36" spine length x 34"</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/4616503296060</id>
      <title>Royal Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1250BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1361</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485448912</id>
    <published>2019-09-18T12:07:29-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-09-18T12:07:29-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/60-1213-p"/>
    <title>American Flag Wool Western Saddle Blanket - Size 34&quot; X 36&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/American_Flag_Wool_Saddle_Blankets.v2.jpg?v=1571609140"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            34.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Show off your patriotic pride with this American Flag saddle blanket. Complete with red, white and blue stripes and white stars. Made by Tahoe Tack. Perfect for western riders at the rodeo who want to stand out in the crowd. Matching saddle and tack available for purchase separately for a complete set!<br><br>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>100% wool for added comfort and durability</li>
<li>These saddle pads are hand woven so the stars and design may differ on each pad</li>
<li>Hand wash and hang dry only</li>
<li>Red, White and Blue American Flag pattern</li>
<li>Size: 34" x 36"</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>34&quot; X 36&quot;</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic Blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western Tack Set</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485448912</id>
      <title>34&quot; X 36&quot;</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1213-P</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2105</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492651024</id>
    <published>2018-06-18T13:19:15-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-18T13:19:15-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/60-co1213-p"/>
    <title>Patriotic American Flag Wool Saddle Blanket Tahoe 36&quot; X 34&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tack Wholesale</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/CO_Saddle-Blanket-Patriotic_043d2dc8-261b-4648-a7b4-e85d843ed14d.jpg?v=1571609185"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tack Wholesale<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            19.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Show off your patriotic pride with this American Flag saddle blanket. Complete with red, white and blue stripes and white stars. <br> <br><strong>The stars are hand made and there will be variations in the star design from blanket to blanket. The overall blanket design may vary from lot to lot as well as the thickness/weight. THE STARS ARE NOT PERFECTLY SHAPED </strong><br>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>Extra large show saddle blanket Size: 34" x 36"</li>
<li>100% Wool Blanket</li>
<li>Hand wash and dry only!</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic Blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Patriotic Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tack Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492651024</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-CO1213-P</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2268</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/94254333968</id>
    <published>2018-02-08T15:34:50-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-02-08T15:34:50-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/tahoe-tack-wild-zebra-horse-saddle-pads-with-wool-top-fleece-padding"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Wild Zebra Horse Western Saddle Pads with Wool Top &amp; Fleece Padding</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Pads</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/1721.jpg?v=1571609218"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Pads<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            34.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h1 style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: #00ff00;"></span></h1>
<h1 style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: #00ff00;"></span></h1>
<p>Bring out your wild side with this stunning zebra print saddle pad. Made from wool with a fleece padding for extra comfort.</p>
<ul>
<li><span class="a-list-item"> Top is made of wool, with shock absorbing wool inside to alleviate pressure </span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item"> Fleece padded underside for horse comfort <br></span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item"> Wear leathers on withers and sides make this pad durable <br></span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Size: 32 x 32 Inch<br></span></li>
</ul>
<p> </p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>clearance</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DESIGN</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Full Horse</s:tag>
    <s:tag>PRINT</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SaddlePadSale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>sale tag</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>White</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Zebra</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/94254333968</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1721BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4990</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/94254333968</id>
      <title>Lime Green</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1721LG</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4990</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/94254333968</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">34.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1721PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4990</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650000</id>
    <published>2017-12-05T15:32:23-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-12-05T15:32:23-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/35-9103"/>
    <title>Tahoe Mini Pony Felt Padded Fleece Lined Western Navajo Saddle Pad 22&quot; x 22&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Pads</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/pony_20saddle_20pads_9c2daea9-d2e6-4965-8057-fabeb5ca5e63.png?v=1571609185"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Pads<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            24.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Keep you and your little ones comfortable with this heavy-duty, felt padded and fleece lined Navajo saddle pad. Features 1-1/4" thick felt center and maize fleece lined, and durable suede wear leathers. Measurements: 22" x 22". 11-inch drop length.<br><br>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>Heavy and durable saddle pad</li>
<li>Thick maize fleece lining for cushion and comfort</li>
<li>1" thick felt padding for shock absorption</li>
<li>Suede wear leathers</li>
<li>Size: 22" x 22". 11" drop length</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Mini &amp; Pony Western Riding</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>pony saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650000</id>
      <title>Red/Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>35-9103-RD/BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2041</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650000</id>
      <title>Purple/Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>35-9103-PU/BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2041</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650000</id>
      <title>Tan/Brown</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>35-9103-TN/BR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2041</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650000</id>
      <title>Blue/Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>35-9103-BL/BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2041</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9492650000</id>
      <title>Grey/Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>35-9103-GY/BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2041</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/10004329424</id>
    <published>2017-12-05T15:05:07-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-12-05T15:05:07-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/mini-canvas-contour-cut-western-saddle-pads-by-tahoe"/>
    <title>Mini Canvas Contour Cut Western Saddle Pads by Tahoe Tack - Size 19&quot; X 19&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Pads</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/61-1427Group_38f82936-ce2b-450d-82d4-533cd2290228.jpg?v=1574545535"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Pads<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            29.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ensure the comfort and safety of both your mini horse and rider with the Tahoe Tack Pony Horse Canvas Contour Cut Western Saddle Pad. Perfect for your little ones and their mini horses who want to fit in with the big horses. </span></p>
<p> </p>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">7/8" fleece lining and felt padding under a rugged canvas cover</span></li>
<li>Contoured spine fits snugly against her back; concentric stitching keeps the felt in place to maintain even coverage and shock absorption</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wear leathers are made of genuine leather for increased durability and long-lasting everyday use.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hand wash and hang dry, fleece side up to ensure long-lasting use</span></li>
<li>Measurements: 19" x 19"</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Brown</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Contour Western Saddle Pads</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Mini &amp; Pony Western Riding</s:tag>
    <s:tag>mini saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>miniature</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pink</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Royal Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/10004329424</id>
      <title>Royal Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1426-RBL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1928</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/10004329424</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1426-PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1928</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/10004329424</id>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1426-BR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1928</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/10004329424</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1426-BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1928</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486089296</id>
    <published>2017-12-05T15:00:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-12-05T15:00:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/61-1325"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Heavy-Duty New Zealand Wool Showring Western Saddle Pad with Leather Wears and Number Slot 36&quot; x 34&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Trophy_Pad_5.v2.v2.jpg?v=1595273304"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            69.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IM8TEtI1oMw" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
<p>Impress the judges with out breaking the bank. The Western Trophy Show pad is a great discovery that all Western riders can appreciate! Hand tooled basket weave wear leathers are attached to the pad, and neatly extends into a double layered leather pockets on the rear end on both sides of the pad. The pocket has two layers, a front and back that is capable of holding a 3-5 digit number card inside to smartly display the exhibitors show numbers. USA Leather from Wickett &amp; Craig.</p>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>This pad is made from 100 % New Zealand wool</li>
<li>The hand tooled basket weave wear leathers are made from USA leather</li>
<li>Two layered rear pockets can display a 3 to 5 digit number card.</li>
<li>Size: 36" X 34"</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: #e06666;">********* Colors may vary from lot to lot **********</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pad Summer Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>USA Leather Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486089296</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1325-PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3856</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486089296</id>
      <title>Purple</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1325-PUR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3856</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486089296</id>
      <title>Royal Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1325-RB</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3856</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486089296</id>
      <title>Sand</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1325-SD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3856</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486089296</id>
      <title>Chocolate Brown</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1325-CH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3856</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
    <published>2017-12-05T14:18:19-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-12-05T14:18:19-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/60-1317n"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Navajo Multicolored Handwoven Acrylic Western Saddle Blanket 32&quot; x 64&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/60-1317-All_20Colors-1-2016.jpg?v=1595531951"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            29.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Tightly handwoven Navajo design made with high-quality acrylic material. Size: 32" x 64"  Hand wash and hang dry only. Navajo saddle blankets can also be used as rugs, seat covers, or even wall decor at home! Tightly hand woven acrylic saddle blanket comes in a variety of appealing colors. The Ancient Navajo designs is very popular, available in many color combinations. <br><br>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<li>Size: 32" x 64"</li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">HANDWOVEN - this saddle blanket was hand woven by skilled craftsmen. </span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">DURABLE - this saddle blanket is made of a sturdy double weave acrylic construction, and if hand washed and hang dried, will look attractive and hold up strong for many many years. </span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">PURE ACRYLIC CONSTRUCTION - this blanket is 100% made of handwoven acrylic, which is comfortable on your horses back, as well as strong, and great looking. </span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">CLASSIC NAVAJO DESIGN -these saddle blankets feature an attractive and classic Navajo print design, making them a perfect addition to any western tack set. </span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">GREAT HOME DECOR - this saddle blanket is perfect for layering over a thicker saddle pad for competitions, parades, holidays, or just wanting to show your country spirit. It also makes a great southwestern style rug for your home! </span></li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>hunter green</s:tag>
    <s:tag>navajo</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Orange</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pink</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Red</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Royal Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pad Summer Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Turquoise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>VTINE</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Black/Grey/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-BK/GY/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Red/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-RD/BK/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Royal Blue/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-BL/BK/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Turquoise/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-TQ/BK/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Pink/Chocolate/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-PK/CH/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Orange/Chocolate/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-OR/CH/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Hunter Green/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-GN/BK/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Pink/Black/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-PK/Bk/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485913488</id>
      <title>Blue/Rust/White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>60-1317-BL/RU/WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3175</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
    <published>2017-12-05T14:15:54-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-12-05T14:15:54-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/61-1220"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Heavy-Duty Solid Color New Zealand Wool Saddle Blanket  36&quot; x 34&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Derby Originals</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/Saddle_Blanket_Extraordinary_Stack.v2.v2.jpg?v=1571609144"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Derby Originals<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            37.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">SIZE AND WEIGHT - this saddle blanket is 36” x 34” and weighs approximately 5 lbs.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWOVEN - these blankets are hand woven by skilled artisans. Due to the nature of making these by hand, there might be slight differences in each product.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">NEW ZEALAND WOOL - 100% of the blanket is made from pure New Zealand wool. Wool from New Zealand is known to be stronger, thicker, and whiter. This allows the color after dying to be clean and clearer than darker wools, and the wool fibers are strong and durable.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">HANDWASH AND DRY ONLY - to keep this product in the best condition it requires hand washing and hang drying only.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">MULTIPLE COLOR OPTIONS - these saddle blankets come in a variety of colors: Green, Black, Red, Pink, Royal Blue, Sweet Pink, and Raspberry. The colors appear bright and clear on the fine wool blankets.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tahoe Tack Heavy-Duty Solid Color  Pure New Zealand Wool Saddle Blankets are made with heavy duty wool by Tahoe. Lowest price for these heavy-duty saddle blankets! They come in the size 36" x 34" and weigh approximately 5 lbs. To keep this product in good care it requires only hand washing and drying. It comes in multiple colors including  Green, Black, Red, Pink, Royal Blue, Sweet Pink, and Raspberry all appearing bright and clear on the soft, durable, and hand-woven New Zealand wool.</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Derby Originals</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Green</s:tag>
    <s:tag>horse blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>New Zealand wool</s:tag>
    <s:tag>New Zealand wool horse blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pink</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Raspberry</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Royal Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pad Summer Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SaddlePadSale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>solid color blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Sweet Pink</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>western saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>wool blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2168</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Royal Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2200</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Green</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-GR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3302</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2685</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Raspberry</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-RA</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2449</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Sweet Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-SPK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2835</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Rust</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-RU</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2168</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9485900240</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1220-RD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2168</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9659673872</id>
    <published>2017-07-08T10:32:56-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-07-08T10:32:56-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/heavy-new-zealand-wool-saddle-blankets-zee-bar-36-x-34"/>
    <title>Zee Bar Design New Zealand Wool Saddle Blanket 36&quot; X 34&quot;</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Blankets</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/New_Zealand_Zee_Bar.jpg?v=1595273234"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Blankets<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This stylish heavyweight woven 100% New Zealand Wool saddle blanket with Zee Bar design, would be a great <g class="gr_ gr_12 gr-alert gr_spell gr_inline_cards gr_run_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del" id="12" data-gr-id="12">show piece</g> or a hit in the trails! Perfect for western riders who like the stylish and traditional old school look. Compatible with most saddle pads and horses.  Great <g class="gr_ gr_13 gr-alert gr_spell gr_inline_cards gr_run_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace" id="13" data-gr-id="13">multi purpose</g> saddle blanket for any riding occasion. </span></p>
<hr>
<ul class="list-unstyled product-feautres-list">
<li>
<i class="fa fa-check"></i><span> </span>Size: 36" x 34"</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Made with 100% New <g class="gr_ gr_14 gr-alert gr_spell gr_inline_cards gr_run_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del multiReplace" id="14" data-gr-id="14">zealand</g> wool</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">These are <g class="gr_ gr_15 gr-alert gr_spell gr_inline_cards gr_run_anim ContextualSpelling ins-del" id="15" data-gr-id="15">hand made</g> so design and colors may vary</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hand wash and dry only to ensure <g class="gr_ gr_16 gr-alert gr_spell gr_inline_cards gr_run_anim ContextualSpelling" id="16" data-gr-id="16">longer</g> lasting durability</span></li>
<li>
<span></span>Blanket weight is about 5 pounds.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brown</s:tag>
    <s:tag>clearance</s:tag>
    <s:tag>CM</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>saddle blanket</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9659673872</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1216 B8-1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5897</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9659673872</id>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1216-B8-4</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5897</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
    <published>2017-07-07T17:06:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-07-07T17:06:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/61-1428"/>
    <title>Tahoe Tack Western Canvas Contoured Wool Felt Extra Comfort Saddle Pad</title>
    <s:type>Saddle Pads</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Tahoe Tack</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/products/61-1428_All_530x_2x_c984029e-a9b8-40d1-b78f-5702589a2881.jpg?v=1571609170"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Tahoe Tack<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Saddle Pads<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            42.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="feature" data-feature-name="twister"></div>
<div class="feature" data-feature-name="twister"></div>
<div id="twister_feature_div" class="feature" data-feature-name="twister">
<div>This Contour western saddle pad is one of the best on the market. It is perfect for any rider providing ultimate comfort for both the horse and the rider. This contour saddle pad is available in seven beautiful colors: black, brown, pink, purple, royal blue, red, or tan. The saddle pad is even washable if need. Just hand wash and hang dry on the fleece side up. They are perfect for any color western saddle whether your saddle is fancy and detailed or a plain color saddle. Your saddle pad color can tell a lot about your personality. You will not be disappointed in fact you will even come back for another color. <span style="font-weight: 400;">This rugged saddle pad is made of a 7/8" fleece lining topped with a rugged canvas top and genuine leather wears, and features a soft fleece lining to keep your horse as comfortable as possible. These pads are both contoured to fit the back, and stitched to promote maximum shock absorption.</span>
</div>
<div></div>
<div>
<ul>
<li>FEATURES - This contour saddle pad features a 7/8" fleece lining as well as genuine distressed leather tan wear leathers. </li>
<li>SIZE - The spine measures 32" long with a total width length of 34". This sizing is typically used for a full horse.</li>
<li>COLORS - This pad is available in seven fun colors for every personality. The colors available are black, brown, pink, purple, tan, or red. </li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<h4><span style="color: #990000;">Instructions:</span></h4>
<blockquote>
<div style="text-align: left;"><em> Hand wash and hang dry, fleece side up</em></div>
<div style="text-align: left;"><em></em></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: #e06666;"><em>********* Colors may vary from lot to lot **********</em></span></div>
</blockquote>
<ul class="product-features-list">
<ul></ul>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Black Friday Sale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brown</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Contour Western Saddle Pads</s:tag>
    <s:tag>coupon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>LargeVolumeWT</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pink</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Purple</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Red</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Red White and Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saddle Pads Year End</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tahoe Tack</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>VTINE</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Western saddle pad</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Award</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Year End Western Pads</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-BK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Brown</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-BR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Pink</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-PK</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-RD</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-RBL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Purple</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-PR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/9486289808</id>
      <title>Tan</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">42.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>61-1428-TN</s:sku>
      <s:grams>3810</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
