<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational.atom"/>
  <title>Tack Wholesale - Educational</title>
  <updated>2019-12-19T13:37:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Tack Wholesale</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/the-importance-of-grooming-your-dog</id>
    <published>2019-12-19T13:37:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-19T13:37:10-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/the-importance-of-grooming-your-dog"/>
    <title>The Importance of Grooming Your Dog</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lydia Dunnivan</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Keeping your pooch well-groomed is a necessity if you want to help keep your dog healthy, happy, and keep easily preventable mats, tangles, and other issues at bay. Today, we’ll be discussing why regularly grooming your dog is beneficial, and showing you the best tools for the job.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/the-importance-of-grooming-your-dog">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keeping your pooch well-groomed is a necessity if you want to help keep your dog healthy, happy, and keep easily preventable mats, tangles, and other issues at bay. Today, we’ll be discussing why regularly grooming your dog is beneficial, and showing you the best tools for the job.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many pet owners with short-haired dogs do not see grooming as something that is necessary, but grooming is vital to maintaining a healthy coat, skin, and nails, and it also gives you the opportunity to pay closer attention to your dog's body to spot potential issues early on. For longer haired dogs and breeds with double coats, grooming is even more important in order to prevent painful tangles and matted fur, and in turn, skin bruising and discoloration and skin irritation and sores, from occurring.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keeping your dog's nails trimmed is also important for their comfort, as overgrown nails can cause a lot of pain as your dog walks and cause them to develop an unnatural gait to cope. In addition, regularly brushing your dog's teeth is a great way to help improve dental health, prevent the spread of dental disease, and develop trust with your pet so that you can inspect their mouth for tooth and gum issues.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Below, we’ve listed some of our staff-favorite “must-have” grooming tools and described their uses, so that you can find the grooming tools that are ideal for your dog's needs!</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/99-1004-99-1005</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CuteNfuzzy’s de-shedding comb is ideal for use with cats, as well as both short and long-haired dogs. These combs feature stainless steel blades that are designed to remove all of your pet’s dead and loose hair without damaging their topcoat.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/double-sided-pet-grooming-brush</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CuteNfuzzy’s double-sided pet grooming brush is a staple brush for any dog owner! One side of the brush features stainless steel teeth that separate and untangle unruly hair, which is perfect for longer haired dogs, while the other side features bristles that are ideal for daily coat brushing and maintenance and help to bring out the shine in your dog's coat.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/pet-dematting-comb-by-cutenfuzzy</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tangles are bound to happen at some point for longer furred dogs, and when they do, CuteNfuzzy’s de-matting brush comes to the rescue with nine stainless steel wave-shaped blades that easily break through mats.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/99-1006</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CuteNfuzzy’s soft, ergonomic grip pet nail clippers feature sharp stainless steel blades for quick and painless nail trimming on any size of dog or cat. For bonus safety, these pet nail clippers feature a secure locking mechanism for safe storage.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tackwholesale.com/products/self-cleaning-pet-slicker-brush</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For everyday coat maintenance, CuteNfuzzy’s self-cleaning pet slicker brushes are our #1 choice due to their wire brush design that easily picks up loose fur and dander without harming the hair coat, and self-cleaning push-button function.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To view the rest of our pet grooming tools available for purchase, view the link below! If you have any further questions, please contact us at </span><a href="mailto:tackman@tackwholesale.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tackman@tackwholesale.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or by phone at (330)-494-8225, we’re always happy to help!</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tackwholesale.com/collections/pet-grooming</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-4-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-weight-for-your-horse</id>
    <published>2019-12-19T10:33:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-19T10:35:18-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-4-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-weight-for-your-horse"/>
    <title>Choosing the Perfect Blanket: Part 4, How to Choose the Right Blanket Weight for Your Horse</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lydia Dunnivan</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making sure you pick the right blanket weight will help ensure your horse is comfortable and properly protected from the elements. In just a few simple steps, we're going to teach you how to choose the correct blanket weight for your horse.</span></h3><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-4-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-weight-for-your-horse">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you have learned how to size your horse for a blanket and get the correct blanket size for your horse, you will need to learn how to identify the blanket that best fits your horse’s individual needs.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some factors to consider when deciding on a blanket model are:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TYPE: Will you be using this blanket for your horse when they are indoors, outside, or both?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">MATERIAL/STRENGTH: Is your horse destructive on blankets? Will your horse be around other horses who are destructive on blankets?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">WEIGHT: How cold is the average daytime and nighttime temperature in your area? Does your horse have a full winter coat or are they body clipped?</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you have had time to consider and think over these important factors for determining what type blanket your horse needs, we will go over each of these factors and detail what blankets you should choose based on your responses.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this section of this series, we will cover how to choose a blanket weight.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>How cold are the average daytime and nighttime temperatures in your area? Does your horse have a full winter coat or are they body clipped?</b></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After choosing the material you want your blanket to be made from, the next most important thing to decide is what fill your horse’s blanket will need to have. The “fill” of a blanket refers to the inner filling that is designed to provide extra warmth.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fill you need largely depends on the temperature in your areas, as well as your horse’s body condition, cold tolerance, and the thickness of their hair coats. Below is a chart showing what fill weight is recommended for clipped and unclipped horses down to a certain temperature.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Please note this chart is a general guideline and if your horse is older, in poor condition, or has a very thin coat that otherwise makes it harder for them to regulate their temperature, they may need a warmer blanket than what is recommended.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1898/9069/files/Capture.JPG?v=1576769537" alt=""></span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know the blanket weight you need, you’re one step closer to finding the perfect blanket to suit your horse! Up next, learn how to identify the fill/weight of blanket that your horse needs.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have any further questions about what blanket your horse should wear, please contact us at </span><a href="mailto:tackman@tackwholesale.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tackman@tackwholesale.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or by phone at (330)-494-8225, we’re always happy to help!</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-3-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-strength-for-your-horse</id>
    <published>2019-12-19T10:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-19T10:30:56-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-3-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-strength-for-your-horse"/>
    <title>Choosing the Perfect Blanket: Part 3, How to Choose the Right Blanket Strength for Your Horse</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lydia Dunnivan</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making sure you pick the right blanket material will help ensure your horse is comfortable and properly protected from the elements. In just a few simple steps, we're going to teach you how to choose the correct blanket material for your horse.</span></h3><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-3-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-strength-for-your-horse">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you have learned how to size your horse for a blanket and get the correct blanket size for your horse, you will need to learn how to identify the blanket that best fits your horse’s individual needs.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some factors to consider when deciding on a blanket model are:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TYPE: Will you be using this blanket for your horse when they are indoors, outside, or both?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">MATERIAL/STRENGTH: Is your horse destructive on blankets? Will your horse be around other horses who are destructive on blankets?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">WEIGHT: How cold is the average daytime and nighttime temperature in your area? Does your horse have a full winter coat or are they body clipped?</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you have had time to consider and think over these important factors for determining what type blanket your horse needs, we will go over each of these factors and detail what blankets you should choose based on your responses.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this section of this series, we will cover how to choose a blanket based on material/strength.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Is your horse destructive on blankets? Will your horse be around other horses who are destructive on blankets?</b></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If your horse has a tendency to rip/damage blankets or will be around another horse who is known to do this, you should not purchase a blanket made of a softer or easier to damage material such as fleece, cotton, or a nylon or poly material that is not ripstop. If your horse is gentle with blankets and this will not be an issue, blanket strength is not as important for you.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Below, we will outline the different common blanket materials that are available and describe their strength. Each material has been given a rating of 1-5, with five being the strongest.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fleece: fleece is a soft, breathable, and highly absorbent material that is ideal for providing warmth without overheating. Fleece is easy to rip/tear if it becomes caught on something or if a horse grabs it. Rating: 1.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">420D Nylon/Poly: 420D material is soft and has a silky feel, it is typically used for stable blankets. 420D can rip/tear if it becomes caught on something or if a horse grabs it. Rating: 2.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canvas: canvas is a rugged material that is very popular for blankets and is most often used indoors or in dry climates. Canvas is tougher than other materials but can still rip and tear. Rating: 3.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">600D Ripstop Nylon/Poly: 600D Ripstop material is commonly used for turnouts because it is strong and designed for outdoor use, and the Ripstop weave helps to prevent rips and tears. Rating: 4.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">1200D Ripstop Nylon/Poly: 1200D Ripstop material is commonly used for turnouts because it is extremely strong and designed for outdoor use, and the Ripstop weave helps to prevent rips and tears. Rating: 5.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know the blanket strength you need, you’re one step closer to finding the perfect blanket to suit your horse! Up next, learn how to identify the fill/weight of blanket that your horse needs.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have any further questions about what blanket your horse should wear, please contact us at </span><a href="mailto:tackman@tackwholesale.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tackman@tackwholesale.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or by phone at (330)-494-8225, we’re always happy to help!</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-2-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-type-for-your-horse</id>
    <published>2019-12-19T10:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-19T10:30:47-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-2-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-type-for-your-horse"/>
    <title>Choosing the Perfect Blanket: Part 2, How to Choose the Right Blanket Type for Your Horse</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lydia Dunnivan</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making sure you purchase the right blanket type will help ensure your horse is comfortable and properly protected from the elements. In just a few simple steps, we're going to teach you how to choose the correct blanket type for your horse.</span></h3><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-2-how-to-choose-the-right-blanket-type-for-your-horse">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you have learned how to size your horse for a blanket and get the correct blanket size for your horse, you will need to learn how to identify the blanket that best fits your horse’s individual needs.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some factors to consider when deciding on a blanket model are:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TYPE: Will you be using this blanket for your horse when they are indoors, outside, or both?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">MATERIAL/STRENGTH: Is your horse destructive on blankets? Will your horse be around other horses who are destructive on blankets?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">WEIGHT: How cold is the average daytime and nighttime temperature in your area? Does your horse have a full winter coat or are they body clipped?</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you have had time to consider and think over these important factors for determining what type blanket your horse needs, we will go over each of these factors and detail what blankets you should choose based on your responses.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this section of this series, we will cover how to choose a blanket type.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Will you be using this blanket for your horse when they are indoors, outside, or both?</b></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are two main blanket types: Turnout and Stable blankets. These are available in a wide array of styles, materials, sizes, colors, etc.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Turnout blankets are waterproof blankets made from sturdy materials and are designed to be used outdoors where they will protect your horse against the elements while standing up to rough play from other horses. Turnout blankets can also be used indoors but because they are often heavier, they can make a horse sweat if the weather warms up.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stable blankets are blankets that are designed for indoor use and are not waterproof and are made from softer and more breathable materials that allow your horse to stay warm without overheating in a warmer indoor environment. Stable blankets are not designed for outdoor use and will often not withstand rough play between horses.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you are looking for a blanket to use in the stall with your horse and they are not destructive, then a stable blanket will suit your needs well, but if you are looking for a blanket to use both indoors and out, or outside in the pasture, then a turnout blanket would be best.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know the blanket style you need, you’re one step closer to finding the perfect blanket to suit your horse! Up next, learn how to identify the strength of blanket that your horse needs.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have any further questions about what blanket your horse should wear, please contact us at </span><a href="mailto:tackman@tackwholesale.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tackman@tackwholesale.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or by phone at (330)-494-8225, we’re always happy to help!</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-1-how-to-measure-your-horse-for-a-blanket</id>
    <published>2019-12-11T16:13:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-19T10:22:50-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-1-how-to-measure-your-horse-for-a-blanket"/>
    <title>Choosing the Perfect Blanket: Part 1, How to Measure Your Horse for a Blanket</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lydia Dunnivan</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making sure your horse blanket fits correctly will help ensure your horse is comfortable and properly protected from the elements. In just a few simple steps, we're going to teach you how to get the most accurate measurement for your horse.<br></span></h3><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.tackwholesale.com/blogs/educational/choosing-the-perfect-blanket-part-1-how-to-measure-your-horse-for-a-blanket">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making sure your horse blanket fits correctly will help ensure your horse is comfortable and properly protected from the elements. All of the blankets we sell follow a uniform measuring system that is given in inches, so once you know your horse’s blanket size, any blanket you purchase in that size should fit your horse.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To properly measure your horse, you will need the following tools:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A helper to help hold the measuring tape or keep your horse still</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A cloth measuring tape</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instructions for Measuring</span></p>
<br>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">For the most accurate results make sure your horse is standing still and square with their head up, on even ground, before you begin measuring. It also never hurts to measure twice to be sure your measurement is correct!</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Place the beginning of the measuring tape squarely at the center point of your horse’s chest, and have someone hold it securely.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bring the measuring tape back across your horse to their flank, making sure to take the measuring tape over the widest part of the shoulder and belly, and keep it taut and not loose across their body.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hold the end of the measuring tape up to the end of your horse’s buttock at the widest point. The closest full inch size to this measurement (chest to rear) will be your horse’s blanket size.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">If your horse has a measurement that is not exact, for example, 68.5”, you will want to preferably size up (not down) to the closest blanket size. In this example, this would be size 69”.</span></li>
</ol>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know your horse’s blanket size, you’re one step closer to finding the perfect blanket to suit your horse! Up next, learn how to identify the type, strength, and weight of blanket that your horse needs.</span></p>
<br><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have any further questions about how to measure your horse or what size blanket your horse should wear, please contact us at </span><a href="mailto:tackman@tackwholesale.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tackman@tackwholesale.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or by phone at (330)-494-8225, we’re always happy to help!</span>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
